<odoo>
    <record id="repair_term_default" model="tech.repair.term">
        <field name="name">Repair Information</field>
        <field name="contenuto">
            <![CDATA[
            <p><strong>ATTENTION: Keep this note to exercise the right to collect the product.</strong></p>

            <h3>Information:</h3>
            <p>We inform you that, after carrying out the necessary checks on your product, we will contact you and inform you of the cost estimate for repairing any anomalies found not during acceptance.<br/>

            <strong>Should you NOT proceed, for any reason, with the repair, the cost of the diagnostic CHECK-UP performed by our professional technicians is € 20.00.</strong></br>

            Please note that we will not be held responsible for any data and/or program losses that have not been declared as TO BE SAVED when the device was loaded by one of the TECH 3 collaborators.<br/>

            We also invite you to collect your product at our location within 10 days from the date of our communication.<br/>
            <strong>After the aforementioned period, all responsibility for your product is declined.</strong></p>

            <p>"The loaner device is provided for <strong>TEMPORARY</strong> and <strong>NON-CONTINUOUS</strong> use at the agreed price.<br/>
            For any damage and/or tampering carried out on the loaner device in question during the granted period, a sum of money equal to the value of the damage itself estimated by TECH 3.0 Srl will be paid, or if deemed irreparable by them, the amount for the entire value of the asset will be due.</p>

            <p><strong>For all replaced components, a limited warranty of 90 days from the date of replacement is guaranteed.</strong><br/>

            The warranty does not cover any defects that arise, for example, due to improper use by the consumer or third parties.</p>

            <p>By signing this form, the recipient is automatically authorized to process the personal data entered. Declares to have received from the Data Controller the information referred to in art.13 of Legislative Decree 196/2003, regarding the purposes and methods of processing personal and sensitive data and, consents to such processing and their communication to third parties.<br/>
            By signing this form, all conditions present in this information are automatically accepted.</p>

            <p>TECH 3.0 Srl operates in compliance with the new European Regulation GDPR n. 679/2016. For any information in this regard, please contact us at the email address: info@techtre.it</p>
            ]]>
        </field>
        <field name="predefinita">True</field>
    </record>
</odoo>
